An attack breaks out
at Northern Women's Prison.
A newly admitted inmate,
during choir tryouts,
attacked prison staff
with a sharp weapon.
SHARING LOVE BEFORE MOTHER'S DAY
Thank you for waiting.
A warm round of applause
for Northern Women's Prison,
Sunshine Women's Choir.
Up next,
Guitar Club, from Class 3-A,
the pitch-perfect Tseng Zi-Ching
will give a great performance.
Give it up for her.
Here we go.
One, two,
three, four,
five, six,
-seven,
-Good. eight,
nine, ten.
Good.
Again.
-Keep going.
-Good. Keep going.
-Almost there. Almost.
-Good.
One more time.
Come on, keep it up.
I can see the head!
Okay, pant.
The baby's head is out.
Pant.
Relax.
Ms. Li Hui-Zhen.
The baby looks healthy.
No birthmarks. She's a girl.
Born a little early.
We'll monitor her in the incubator.
Don't worry.
MOJ WOMEN'S PRISON
-Yun-Shi.
-Happy birthday.
One year old.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday…
Good grief.
A truck run over your throat?
That was awful.
You made her cry.
You squeal like a pig.
You scared the kid to tears.
-Come on.
-That bad?
-Okay, don't cry.
-It's awful.
If you're so great, you sing.
I could sing through my nose and
sound better.
Sing it.
Yun-Shi, listen to this.
Happy birthday to you
Wishing you
Happy
Birthday
Every day
See? She loves it.
She's smiling.
WISDOM GATE
Take the money.
Financial freedom.
Life will be stress-free.
Be a doctor. Earn your keep.
Doctor's good.
Hat.
-Studying is important.
-Get a PhD.
Yun-Shi, over here.
You want that one?
You crazy? Who put handcuffs here?
I did. Too few items.
How'd I know she'd take it?
You can't put handcuffs.
-Stupid.
-Yeah.
All right.
That didn't count.
One more time.
Let's try again, okay?
-Right.
-Pick again.
Let's do it again.
Which one do you want?
Nice.
Grow up to be a musician.
Piano.
She can play piano.
She could be a singer too, right?
Then I'll be a stage mom.
-Piano…
-Musician.
-Musician is great.
-Piano's good.
Awesome.
Great, who put that in?
Me. Pretty impressive, huh?
You're the best.
During lock-up,
I saw some defects in Workshop Six.
So I brought one back.
That's stealing.
-I'm taking it.
-No.
It's scratched. It's ruined.
-It's broken.
-Let her have it.
-It's all broken anyway.
-I saw nothing.
Thank you.
Gorgeous.
Yun-Shi, play the piano.
Do-Re-Mi
Okay, everyone look here.
Come on, Yun-Shi.
One. Two.
Three.
Can't wait.
Done with the cake.
Other than Yun-Shi,
the rest of you owe me.
Me?
Who else? Hey.
You know how much this cake cost me?
A whole week's labor pay.
We'll pay, stop nagging.
What are you, Miss Moneybags?
Cake is a luxury here.
Like LV, you know?
Of course I know LV.
I carry one daily.
A regular gave me one.
You got that?
Maybe he gave you fakes.
-What.
-Let me tell you.
I've got more than LV.
Chanel too.
And Hermès.
All scams.
Eat shit.
Sold sex for LV? Think I don't know?
-I didn't.
-Then where'd the money come from?
-Grandma. Look at her.
-A-Pei.
-Don't be so harsh.
-Okay.
Don't forget,
you only took 15 minutes off.
Photo's done.
Open up.
Chief Fang.
So cute.
This one here.
You see yourself?
-You want it?
What are you doing?
Stand aside.
Cell inspection.
Yes.
Polaroid.
Chen Yu-Wen.
Their 15 minutes are up.
Why are you still loitering here?
There's plum wine.
All the contraband's here.
Plum wine?
Giving the plums a bath.
Fuck!
Still joking?
-Take it away.
-Yes.
Who let you take pictures?
Reporting, Chief Fang.
I took that.
Write a report when you go back.
Yes.
Chief.
Don't we have human rights?
Human rights?
Of course you do.
But do you respect them?
Theft, fraud, threats, murder.
Think this is a vacation?
Know your place.
What?
Want to hit me?
Come on. Do it.
-Misunderstanding.
-Of course not.
-Hui-Zhen, it's fine.
-Squat down.
Fifty squat jumps, now.
No.
-Her leg's bad, we'll jump for her.
-Yeah.
So loving, huh?
Make it 100.
-Fifty.
-Still bargaining?
It's okay.
-I can.
-Fine, 100.
-Sis, okay?
-Sorry.
-No problem.
-Count off.
One.
8112.
Don't think having a child
entitles you to special treatment.
I'm telling you,
break the rules, and I'll make it worse.
Two.
Didn't you eat?
Louder.
Three.
Four.
Five.
I'll be blunt.
Send the child out soon.
It's better for her.
You said before the age of three,
I can still care for her, right?
This is a prison.
Not a place to raise a child.
Don't think keeping her with you
means love.
Seven.
Stand here.
Get in line.
Move it.
What are you staring at?
-Li Guimei.
-Here.
Chen Yuhan.
Here.
Liu You-Xin.
Huang Lijuan.
My legs are killing me.
Chief Fang went too far this time.
Sis, you okay?
Thanks.
-With this age.
-Here, attention.
Count off.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
8918, inside.
Look after her.
What's with that face?
Take off your shoes.
You think you can sit there?
Hey.
Leave me alone.
-What the hell?
-A-Lan.
Keep it down.
There's a child here.
Sis.
She still needs rules.
Or she'll overstep.
Hey.
Your name?
How did you end up here?
Are you mute or deaf?
Do you know the rules?
Quit glaring at me,
you crazy bitch.
A-Pei. No.
She's a child.
Take it slow.
What's your name?
I'm talking to you.
Are you mute?
Let go.
-What?
-Can't you understand?
-Let go.
-What the hell?
No.
I said no.
We'll lose points.
What?
You're raising a kid in prison?
None of your business.
She'll hate you when she grows up.
Can't believe it.
Crazy bitch.
What did you say?
Are you crazy?
She'll hate you when she grows up.
Someone's coming.
What's the fuss?
Sit.
It's okay.
Quiet.
What?
Not happy sleeping by the toilet?
Saved the best spot for you.
6,000 for this spot.
Deal?
Not bad.
Or this one, 5,000.
Okay, don't cry.
Can we sleep or what?
Damn it.
-Too loud? Leave!
-What's your problem?
Never seen a kid cry?
Lunatic.
What?
What's all the noise?
Nothing, Chief.
The kid's just fussing before bed.
Quiet down.
Okay, okay.
It's okay.
All right, let's sleep.
Okay, you're okay.
Fall in.
Headcount.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
Second shift.
Open up.
-Hello, Chief.
Move it in the back.
Keep up.
8918.
You doubting me?
Yun-shi.
You making bread too?
Squad leader.
Here.
You train the newbie.
Yes, ma'am.
8134.
Go help over there.
Like this.
And this.
Done.
Are you folding or not?
You stupid?
You just said like this!
Are you really that dumb?
Heard your mom dumped you as a kid.
Must be 'cause you're dumb.
Even pigs are smarter.
What do you mean?
-That's what I said.
-What?
What's with the mess?
Stand against the wall.
Face the wall.
Everyone, eat.
Hello, classmates.
Enjoy your meal.
You're the best.
Tasty.
No talking.
Ouch.
Look at her.
So skinny.
So pale. Poor thing.
Not eating.
Not eating? That's not good.
I can't.
Then let her have mine.
Give it all to her.
Here, eat, eat.
Eat a little more.
Will you stop?
Damn.
What the hell?
Kill her!
Crazy bitch.
Stop fighting.
All right, all right.
A-Lan, guard's coming.
-Hurry!
-You wanna die?
What?
-Stop fighting.
-You crazy?
Finish her!
Hui-Zhen.
-Fight in the cafeteria.
-Die!
Control, requesting backup.
Hand me the kid.
Watch out.
No. Hui-Zhen.
Stop fighting.
Hui-Zhen.
Let go.
What are you doing?
Grandma.
Let me go.
Okay, let's take a look.
Okay.
Let me see here.
It's swollen.
Does it hurt?
Yun-Shi has minor bruises.
Nothing serious.
Well…
Since she hit her head, to be safe.
I also checked her eyes.
What's wrong with her eyes?
I found clouding in Yun-Shi's left eye.
I suspect a congenital cataract.
From this examination,
I found Yun-Shi's vision is blurry.
It's possible it's amblyopia.
How is this possible?
Cataracts can run in families.
Amblyopia has many causes.
Yun-Shi was premature.
It could be from being in
the incubator too long.
It delayed her vision.
Can this be treated?
We can correct the vision difference
with glasses.
But for the cataracts,
we'll need surgery.
But this is a prison.
We don't have the equipment.
Without proper treatment,
it could cause permanent vision loss.
How are you feeling?
Hui-Zhen.
Don't worry.
8112.
8918.
I announce
both of you lose 0.5 points
in conduct and reformation.
Total one point each.
Seven days in the
disciplinary cell.
Chief Fang.
Docking points is fine.
But the disciplinary cell?
Yun-Shi's sick. I have to care for her.
You're bargaining with me?
I told you already.
This is prison. No place for a child.
-Take her back to the ward.
-Yes.
-Yun-Shi, where does it hurt?
-8918, come here.
Tell Grandma, okay?
Tell Grandma if it hurts.
-Go.
-If anything hurts…
Grandma.
-Go.
-Watch Yun-Shi for me.
I will.
-Don't worry.
-8024.
Any pain?
You want a divorce?
Go fuck yourself.
Get an abortion.
We'll monitor her in the incubator.
It could cause permanent vision loss.
No place for a child.
She'll hate you.
Let me go.
Requesting backup.
Let me die.
8918.
ZHONG CELLBLOCK
A love letter.
Pen pal.
What year is this? Pen pals?
It's that young lawyer defending me.
Look, so handsome.
My Michael.
I can't see.
Why are you writing to him?
Who else can I write to?
I don't have family.
He was the last person I saw
before coming in.
And I wrote to him first.
I didn't expect him to write back.
What's this?
Rap lyrics.
He's a lawyer, but he does hip-hop.
You rap. I'll beatbox.
I'll give you a tempo.
Come on.
A-Lan, behind bars you watch the stars
I plead justice in court
-Listen up.
-Buzzkill.
-We just started.
-To be continued.
Headcount.
-One.
-Two.
Three.
That's about it.
Yun-Shi.
Mom's back.
-Thank you.
-Such a good kid.
The best.
Why the eye patch?
The doctor said Yun-Shi has
a vision difference.
They don't have
the corrective glasses yet.
Cover the good eye first.
Use the weaker eye.
This trains it.
For how long?
Don't worry.
For now, one to two hours daily.
The doctor said
it's the basic treatment.
The doctor also said,
to get better,
she needs long-term treatment outside.
Were you good?
Yeah, she was.
She was drawing.
-Look, she drew these.
-Look at that flower.
-You drew it, didn't you?
-Pretty, right?
Feeling any better?
Did you draw this?
What's up with your forehead?
You don't speak?
So rude, ignoring people.
Sis. Forget her.
This crazy bitch is on another level.
Just carry one bag yourself.
It's heavy, newbie.
Only one? Really?
Your other hand is empty.
You deaf?
Take it.
What you staring at?
Hurry up, okay?
Staring. Still staring.
Not happy, huh?
Cocky.
She's next level.
Don't know how to sort trash?
Move.
-Where to?
-I'm talking to you.
I'm talking to you. You deaf?
What do you want?
Hit me.
Hit you? Kick her.
Sort the trash.
-What's with this bitch?
-What?
What's this bitch up to?
So bad, huh?
Put it down.
You nuts?
Drop it.
-Want life in prison?
-Put it down.
So bad, huh.
Put that down.
Swing that at me one more time.
-Don't be stupid.
-Hit her.
Hit her!
-It's her fault.
-Enough.
Grab the tube.
Wanna get locked up?
Enough.
You go first.
-Going where?
-Enough.
-Go first.
-What are you doing?
-What?
What, you bleeding heart?
She tried to stab me with this.
Hui-Zhen.
I treat you like a sister.
This crazy bitch was swinging this.
Trying to kill us.
What if she hit A-Lan in the face?
How can she still be a hostess?
-I'm not doing that when I'm out.
-Well, you--
Just help her for now.
Can't you see she's hurt?
She's not a bad person.
Stop bullying her.
We were in neighboring cells.
She cried for seven days straight.
Look at the cut on her head.
She kept smashing it against the wall.
She's young. Must've been through a lot
to end up in here.
Stop bullying her.
Try to understand each other.
We're in the same room.
Okay? Sis.
It's all good. You're still pretty.
That kick was too hard.
You told me to do it.
Now you blame me?
Gotta hold back.
-How?
-But you really kicked.
Hey.
You people hungry?
Yeah.
Hungry?
Got cake, A-Yong bought it.
Cake.
He treats you well. He visits often.
We owe each other. Drop it.
Eat. Quit yapping.
A-Lan.
Want one?
You want some?
Sorry.
Thanks.
I'm sorry too.
Make up.
Give her a hug.
Come on.
Grandma, why doesn't she have to?
Yeah.
A-Pei.
Me too.
Okay.
It's just a hug.
Come on, come on.
Don't be shy.
Okay, it's fine.
If it's good, eat a few more.
Sorry…
about what happened.
All right.
Have some cake.
Let's eat.
Yummy, yummy.
Sis, here's a piece.
Okay.
Here.
Look at you, eating it up.
On wings of song
Fly to a place without pain or parting
A garden of red blooms
Dreaming under the quiet moonlight
The lotus flowers
Await their charming little sister
You like it?
-I like.
-Yeah?
Yes.
Look.
Do you like it?
Make a heart.
Heart.
You like it, huh?
Warden.
8112.
What are you doing?
-Sorry.
-Know your place.
It's okay. It's okay.
You there.
You have a question?
I have a question.
Has this year's party program
been set?
Is this year's decided?
Not yet.
What do you want to do?
I'd like to perform with the choir.
I want to sing.
I just saw Yun-Shi
listening to the choir.
She looked happy, really into it.
I want to learn to sing.
Sir.
That's not fair.
We'd like to perform
a dance too.
Can you dance like that?
I can. I can even wave, look.
-Quiet.
-Okay.
It's fine.
Glad to see you all support the event.
I'm happy too.
But we do things fairly here.
Discuss it between you.
Pick one: dance
or sing.
Don't worry, Warden.
In our dorm,
A-Pei sings great.
And Grandma,
she used to be a famous singer,
and even led a choir.
Nice. Good idea.
Then, make a decision soon.
-Okay.
-Thank you, sir.
Goodbye, sir.
Grandma.
Sorry.
I got ahead of myself.
Hui-Zhen,
enough.
You dragged me into it.
Why bring Grandma into this?
Yeah. You sing so badly.
Why start a choir?
Because…
I've decided to send Yun-Shi out early.
Isn't it two more years?
Why the sudden change?
Chief Fang.
I think you're right.
I want to help Yun-Shi
find a new family.
You mean,
you'll send Yun-Shi away early?
Because of her vision?
I want to fix her eyes.
Give her a better place to grow.
That's what I should do as her mom.
My only wish now
is to form a choir.
Give Yun-Shi a proper goodbye.
Hey.
All this time,
just "Dear Michael"?
Starting is hard.
Your English is next level.
I'll help you.
Just write,
"Miss you so much.
My heart itches."
Okay.
I'll write, "going crazy."
The itchy part stays in the heart.
Chief Fang asked me to evaluate.
Is Yun-Shi adjusting well?
Pretty well.
Here you go.
What interests her most?
She's quite into music.
Music?
That's great.
Will she keep the eye patch on?
She may try to rip it off, but…
Out the way.
Hey.
What now?
Something's up.
-Go.
-What is it?
Not enough people yet?
None of your business.
What do you want?
-Get out.
-Relax.
What?
The warden wants us to talk.
I'm talking.
Last year was dance.
The year before too.
You damn idiot.
Telling the warden?
Know how long I trained?
Yeah. Sister Wang trained for half a year.
To score points at the party.
Level up early.
Want points?
Join the choir.
Fuck me.
Singing isn't the same as dancing.
Got a brat,
think you're better than us?
Who's the brat?
-Who?
-Separate, all of you.
It's fine.
-Watch it.
Hey.
Even if it's dance,
I'll sign up for dance.
But the points
will be mine.
So mean.
Back when I ruled the disco,
you weren't even born.
Then show us.
-Bring it on!
-Not afraid of you!
Can you do it?
Come on.
Sir, let us work out.
Exercise.
Just do it. What's the hold up?
Show her.
See that?
Seems pretty good.
We won.
Got long legs, so what?
What?
What are you doing?
You a sore loser.
What the hell?
Exercise time is over.
Fall in.
Still staring?
Line up.
Take your seats.
What's that?
You didn't see?
Middle-school diploma.
-My son graduated?
-Nice.
-Two weeks ago.
-All right.
When you pulled that out,
you scared me here.
-Thought it was a marriage cert.
-I'm innocent, Your Honor.
Are you doing honest work?
-No more scams.
-No.
If you return, who watches the kid?
Keep it down.
I'm done with that.
Good. Hey.
Bring more food next visit.
Yun-Shi wants chicken drumsticks.
They're always starving.
Buy two kg, or more.
It's been about ten years?
All these years, I came to see you,
and you refused my visits.
Why agree to see me now?
Whatever your reason,
it doesn't matter.
I'll still come every year
around this time.
-Because today is--
-The day he died.
The anniversary
of your brother Zhi-Wei's death.
I know.
Also the day you killed Dad
and wrecked my life.
Once more.
Push.
Mom.
You tried to die, but you failed.
And just like that, you were gone.
What about me?
When I was a kid,
the media hounded me all day,
reporters chasing me with questions.
"Why did your celebrity mom murder?"
I lived like a street rat.
Did you know that?
Till we meet again
Take my hand
Watch the warm sunset
As it crosses the hills
The world is wide
I want to walk with you
But time
Always arrives first
To the end
Mom.
Yang Yu-Ying.
Take a look yourself.
You sing and play the piano every day.
Look how you raised the kid.
What kind of mother are you?
PHENYLKETONURIA
MAY CAUSE INTELLECTUAL DISABILITY
What are you doing?
-What the hell?
-Who are you?
Damn it.
You think you're still that big star
on stage?
Keep dreaming.
I'm a doctor,
and you let me lose face.
What the hell?
Keep your kid under control.
Can't even have a normal kid.
You shouldn't have been born.
Why don't you just die?
Till we meet again
Kiss my forehead
The clear sky will
Embrace you and me
If not for you,
I wouldn't have been this strong.
Every year on this day,
I'll come to torment you,
to remind you,
so you always remember,
what a cruel, awful mother you are.
Grandma.
You still like music, right?
Please help me, okay?
The audition's tomorrow. I need you.
No.
I said no.
That's…
enough.
-Can you do this?
-Hold still.
You take so long.
-Damn it.
-Seriously.
-The hell?
-Girls shouldn't curse.
A-Pei.
One, two, three.
-Four. Like this? Or?
-Let me see.
For four beats,
four beats goes like this.
One, two, three, four.
Maybe you should conduct.
Don't think about it.
Can you go with me to tomorrow's audition?
You have the ear for it.
I'll think about it.
Attention, everyone.
Headcount.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
-Grandma.
-Sis.
What happened? Where are they taking you?
It's nothing.
The warden asked for me.
Just a chat, that's all.
Hi, Yun-Shi.
-Turn around.
-Still?
-No kidding.
-Move it.
I'll do it myself, it's faster.
Hui-Zhen.
All right.
I'll be your conductor.
Really?
I'll teach you to sing.
Sis. What happened to you?
It's nothing.
The warden said the last three years,
it's always been dance.
So this year,
they want a change.
Combine singing and dancing.
The warden's so nice.
We can sing?
Sing.
-Dance.
-Grandma.
Will you come to tomorrow's audition?
Of course.
I don't need to look.
Thank you, Grandma.
If Sis goes, I'm going too.
We won't need you, then.
Crazy woman. Move.
I want to hear Sis sing.
Thank you, Grandma.
8648.
Wang Mei-Li.
I'm 8423, Chen Hsin-Ti.
Heard about the audition.
We didn't really prepare.
Sing whatever you can.
I've always been confident
I'm not afraid to say it
But when I'm near you
I suddenly feel shy
Boy you make me so shy
Every time you walk by
How did I get like this?
My body won't listen to me
I've never felt this before
My emotions are out of control
Don't know what you do to me
I just know it feels right
Never felt this way like
I'm outta control
Nice!
Goddess. So good.
Alto, mezzo.
What?
Low. Mid.
We're in?
You're in.
Remember to come to practice.
-That's it?
-That's it.
You stepped on me.
Hands off.
Sunset beyond the hills
Soprano.
Alto.
Why?
Mezzo. Soprano.
Ave Maria
A-Pei.
Tossed and tormented in the sea of love
Mezzo.
What's mezzo?
Means to get off.
-Move.
-No.
Mezzo-soprano.
Bonus points.
Hui-Zhen.
Aren't you singing?
Too many people. I'll sing in the dorms.
Want to learn? Then sing.
Give it a try.
-It's an audition.
-Go try.
8112.
Li Hui-Zhen.
A grateful heart
Thankful for you
With me for life
Gives me courage to be myself
A grateful heart
Thankful for fate
Flowers bloom and fade
I still treasure it
Soprano.
Soprano?
Sure.
I got in?
-But, Hui-Zhen.
-Yeah?
If you don't sing well by then,
we'll take you off.
I'll do my best. Thank you.
Thanks.
Come on, everyone.
Stand by part.
Okay, come on.
Sopranos over there.
Then,
Alto, mezzo.
Sopranos are here.
She's got her hand on me.
Sister Wang.
Mezzo-soprano.
Stand here.
-That side.
-It's fine, just switch.
You're asking Sister Wang move aside?
Why are you pushing?
What are you doing?
Why are you shoving?
Knock it off.
A-Lan. It's A-Lan.
What?
Keep it down.
It's nothing.
Get down all of you. Get down.
Get down.
You're all grown adults.
And you still fight all the time.
Tell me.
How do we become a good choir?
Chemistry.
Grandma, how do we build chemistry?
-Silence. That's chemistry.
-The fuck?
What the hell?
-Okay.
-You got to understand each other.
So today
you all
will introduce yourselves.
Why are you here?
Okay.
Your interests.
Your skills.
Tell us.
Okay?
Hui-Zhen, you go.
-Me?
-Yes.
Okay.
I'm Li Hui-Zhen.
I worked at a securities firm.
I killed my husband.
Hobbies…
I don't have any.
Skills?
Making red bean buns.
Why did you kill your husband?
He traded U.S. stocks.
During the financial crisis,
we lost a lot of money.
We went bankrupt.
I finally got pregnant.
I still want to have the baby.
You know how much debt I have?
How do I raise a kid?
Got it.
You want to use this to divorce me.
So you won't be in debt.
I'm telling you.
I won't let you get your way.
You know what?
She was pregnant then.
He almost killed her.
What a jerk.
Back then,
I was pregnant with Yun-Shi.
He wouldn't let me keep her.
He kept insisting that I abort her.
I refused.
Then he beat me every day.
He kicked me in the stomach.
Want a divorce, huh?
Go away.
-Don't.
-Divorce me.
You want a divorce?
Divorce?
Try it.
Go to hell.
That's it.
Thanks.
Your turn.
My turn?
Me.
Huang Pei-Ying.
Everyone calls me A-Pei.
What else…
Poop…
Poop?
Damn it, mad woman.
You deaf or what?
I said, fraud.
She pooped so much she got locked up.
Done laughing?
Okay, okay.
I was desperate for money.
That's how I started.
I was going to quit.
But got busted instead.
Long Legs, you're up.
A-Lan, Chiu Hsiu-Lan.
I was an escort.
A girl had me smuggle a case of chargers.
-Got caught.
-Yeah right, smuggling batteries.
Thirteen years bit much, no?
Depends what's inside the chargers.
Drugs.
Exactly.
I wanted to score big.
Open a boutique shop one day.
-You'd take that money?
-You stupid?
Damn it, none of your business.
Enough, stop it.
Next.
Sister Wang, you're up.
I don't need cheering.
Your panties got stuck?
That's you.
Your butt's starving.
No.
You've never had a wedgie?
Quit pulling.
We were poor growing up.
I was the eldest of many siblings.
So we all…
had no money for food.
I joined a gang.
Had money to buy food.
I grew up.
Had no skills.
So I collected debts.
Accidentally almost killed someone.
That's why I'm here.
My hobby and skill are dancing.
I joined to compete with her.
Your turn.
She's too young.
She's good. You can skip.
-Why not?
-No need to know.
Scared to speak, kid?
Too scared to say it?
You messed up. You got caught with drugs.
I'm Liu You-Xin.
No hobbies.
Skill, modern ballroom.
No wonder you're so flexible.
Why are you in here?
My mom…
abandoned me when I was little.
Grandma and Dad
raised me.
Grandma died young.
Then Dad had a stroke.
He was paralyzed.
So I borrowed from loan sharks.
Dad passed in the end.
-What?
-Where you going?
-Let go.
-What's wrong with a hug?
-Dad's debt?
-Hands off.
You done?
What you looking at?
What now?
Let go.
Innocent act, huh?
-Get over here.
-What?
This is your life now.
Think you can leave?
Back then,
he didn't give a shit about me.
I was just his toy.
He never saw me as a person.
I had enough. Really.
So I stole his gun.
How old are you?
Nineteen.
Well…
First of all.
Thank you all for joining.
I started this choir
so Yun-Shi
could make good memories
before leaving.
I didn't expect everyone
to be this passionate.
No matter who we were before,
I'm happy to know who you are now.
Let's do our best. Earn points together.
Get out sooner.
Thank you.
Chest up.
Don't stop.
Tuck your belly.
All right.
Report, teacher.
Sister Wang didn't tuck.
I did.
Okay, come on.
-Pick it up here.
-Right.
Let me introduce
our accompanist.
Yu-Wen.
It's you?
So happy
Very Happy
Give a round of applause
This is called a trust game.
Inhale.
Let your belly puff like a balloon.
Exhale…
No, no.
Why so small?
Does this work?
-It works.
-Come on, again.
Inhale. Exhale.
Go, 8648.
Run.
I'm out of breath.
Breathe.
I'm already doing it.
So happy
Very Happy
Let's sing a song
So happy
Very Happy
Singing makes the heart so happy
You take the high note
I'll take the low
Blend them together
Push. Harder.
Push through. You'll be fine.
Right.
Got it.
What a lovely sound
A charming sound
CORRECTIVE GLASSES APPLICATION
You got the money?
The sisters helped.
Such a crisp, lovely sound
Such a crisp sound
A lovely sound
Hey
Hey, you all.
Any ideas for a choir name?
Dream Choir.
No "Freedom Choir."
The hell.
-You have freedom?
-No way.
Go on.
Eighteen Blossoms Choir.
So tacky.
Hey, Iron Ladies.
The Sneeze Choir.
"Choir" in Taiwanese.
I have an idea.
Yes.
Sunshine Women's Choir.
More formal.
Oh, nice.
There's sunshine.
Sunshine.
I'm a Sunshine Girl.
Then it's…
Sunshine Women's Choir.
Please give a warm welcome to
the Sunshine Women's Choir.
Amazing grace
How sweet the sound
That saved a wretch like me
I once was lost
But now am found
T'was blind
But now I see
YEAR-END SKY GIFT
Come train your dancing with me
I come and go without a trace
I'm just a gust of wind
Yup
Just like this
Like splitting a watermelon
Such a simple question
Yup
Just like this
Like flying a kite
Like a bird flying free
Youth is short
No need to be shy
Step in, step out
Skirt short
Don't overthink
Sway with the music
Everybody
Brothers hold onto sisters
Aunties hold onto uncles
Everybody
Train till you're 100
Feeling 18
Come train your dancing with me
I come and go without a trace
I'm not the Dragon Lady
Yup
Just like this
Like splitting a watermelon
Such a simple question
Yup
Just like this
Like flying a kite
Like a bird flying free
Youth is short
No need to be shy
Step in, step out
Skirt short
Don't overthink it
Sway with the music
Everybody
Brothers hold onto sisters
Aunties hold onto uncles
Everybody
Train till you're 100
Feeling 18
Come train your dancing with me
I come and go without a trace
I'm not the Dragon Lady
8112.
Come here. I need a word.
About her?
Yun-Shi still hasn't been placed.
Social Services found an
early intervention children's home.
If we send her now,
will she stay there, or--
They'll keep looking for a family.
Adoption is already hard.
But if you're willing,
they can send Yun-Shi's profile overseas.
-It'd be easier.
-No, no.
Not overseas.
Too far.
I'd never see her again.
Not overseas.
About what you said,
when will she be sent away?
Next month.
So soon?
How's this dress?
Wear a dress.
Suspenders. So pretty.
Look, what's your favorite color?
Purple.
There's a heart.
That's right.
I got you lots of pretty clothes.
These are for later.
You'll wear them when you're older.
This is where you're going.
Many people will care for you there.
They'll treat you well.
Many teachers…
8112 is here.
It's okay.
The teacher from
the Caring Children's Home.
They'll take care of Yun-Shi.
8112.
What are you doing?
We want to…
go back to the workshop.
You asked to send her early.
Now you regret it?
It's not up to you.
Chief Fang.
Please.
Let me and Yun-Shi…
stay a few more days.
Just a few days, okay?
Any number of days is fine.
Okay.
But your daughter?
How long can her eye wait?
Come sign the papers.
Ms. Li. Don't worry.
We'll take good care of her.
I'll hold you.
Where do I sign?
ADOPTION PARTY: LI
I want Mommy.
Done.
Paperwork's done.
You can take her now.
-Wait.
-8112.
-Let me talk to her.
-Enough.
-Yun-Shi.
-Mommy.
Okay. Give them a moment.
Mommy.
Don't cry.
I don't want to.
I don't want to. I want Mommy.
Okay. Yes.
Don't forget Mommy, okay?
-Eat well.
-I want Mommy.
I want Mommy.
-Take care of your eyes.
-Take her.
Eat well, okay?
Yun-Shi.
8112, enough. You'll scare her.
She forgot this.
8112.
Yun-Shi.
-8112, stay back.
-Yun-Shi.
Yun-Shi.
I'm sorry.
Mommy is sorry.
Yun-Shi.
Yun-Shi. Yun-Shi.
Grow up well.
Yun-Shi.
Yun…
-Run.
-Hey, wait for me.
Tseng Zi-Ching, wait up.
Fen-Fen, hurry. You're so slow.
Chicken drumstick bento.
I'm coming.
Wait for me.
Smells so good.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Two chicken drumstick bento, please.
Wow, so many toppings.
Thank you.
-Hey, you got two mains. Trade with me.
-No.
-Come on, don't be stingy.
That's for running so slow.
Mom.
Auntie.
Happy birthday to you
Make a wish.
Happy birthday.
Come on.
Let's cut the cake.
By the way.
Next week's showcase.
Will you two come?
Of course.
Didn't we promise you?
Can I invite one more person?
Who?
My birth mom.
Zi-Ching.
About that, we think that if--
I'll try to contact her.
Really?
But…
It's been many years.
She hasn't showed up once.
I can't promise she'll come.
I went to see Yun-Shi for you.
She's doing well now.
Her eye treatment continues.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
I wanted to know how she was, too.
By the way, supervisor.
I've been wanting to ask.
Why do you look out for Yun-Shi and me?
You've got the courage I never had.
Back then, I wasn't brave enough.
I didn't have my child.
But I had her.
I didn't give her a healthy body.
I couldn't care for her.
Is that really right?
At least you gave her a future.
By the way,
Yun-Shi's been out for over two years.
No one's adopted her yet.
Is it because
her mother is a murderer?
Finding a new family
takes fate.
Don't worry.
Hui-Zhen.
Stop talking. Come play.
Assemble.
I have an announcement.
The warden
has recommended Sunshine Women's Choir
to perform at the Hope Concert.
Did I sing too well?
You done? Zip it.
In two months, during Mother's Day week,
you'll represent the women's prison
at a concert.
Does this mean we leave?
Duh.
Michael, I'm coming.
Quiet.
8112.
Yes.
You must participate.
I…
Chief Fang.
I don't want to.
Who are you to say no?
Officers.
Take them back.
-Dismissed.
-Yes.
8024.
Take your meds.
Thanks.
Attention, everyone.
8918.
-Visitation.
-Me?
You doubt me?
Are you coming or not?
You-Xin.
You…
Who are you?
I…
I'm your mother.
I'm sorry.
I only recently learned
what happened to you.
I miss you so much.
I wanted to see you.
I want to ask you…
Did you know
Grandma left you
the house in her will?
Do you know this?
So what if I know?
Or don't?
I think
since
you are, well,
you're inside right now.
About the house,
could you
sign it over to me?
You…
You-Xin.
Don't get me wrong.
If we rent the place out,
we can make money.
I'll give the house back when you get out.
Okay?
Stop lying.
You ditched me as a kid.
Never checked on me.
You were nowhere when Grandma
and Dad died.
How dare you show up asking for the house?
You only care about money, not me.
8918, attention.
Quiet, or the visit ends.
You-Xin.
My life has been so hard. You…
Think about when I had you.
I still had to care
for your useless father.
Your grandma was selfish too.
You wouldn't have suffered
if she'd sold it earlier.
You're obsessed with money.
If it sold, where would we have lived?
Sleep on the street?
How much is that place even worth?
It couldn't pay for Dad's treatment.
No, no. You don't know.
A developer is interested in the land.
For luxury condos. Worth a lot.
When you get out,
we'll split it fifty-fifty.
Fifty-fifty okay?
What's wrong?
What happened?
Come.
Tell Grandma.
Why?
Why do I have a mom like this?
I really hate her.
Why?
Don't cry.
She probably doesn't know
how to be a mother yet.
Is Grandma okay?
Why the shot?
She's just seeing the doctor.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
I called you here to tell you.
Yun-Shi found a family.
She did?
What…
What kind of people are they?
Any other kids?
What do they do?
Here, this is her file.
Social Services matched many families
and assessed her as the best fit.
NO CRIMINAL RECORD
Next,
the court will summon you.
You can meet her in person.
Great.
I need the restroom.
Grandma.
Are you okay?
Just old age.
Don't worry.
Grandma.
I passed the infirmary
and saw you on an IV.
You're on more meds too.
Are you sick?
It's nothing.
Don't worry.
I'm really worried.
Grandma.
This is serious.
I'll ask the supervisor
so you can see a doctor outside.
Okay?
Hui-Zhen.
I have liver cancer.
It's terminal.
The tests show stage two liver cancer.
Well…
I suggest a hospital outside
for more detailed tests.
Then we'll know how to treat it.
For liver cancer, a family donor
is also an option.
We can contact your family about that.
It's up to you.
8024.
Yes.
I can help contact your daughter.
Chief Fang.
Thanks. Thank you.
I don't want to
be a burden to my family.
Also,
please don't tell others
that I'm sick.
Please.
Okay.
I even thought about ending my life.
But…
because of you…
seeing you form this choir
for your daughter
and asking me to conduct…
Because of you,
I found music again.
I want to thank you.
I can still make
my final moments meaningful.
This was the time
I felt most human.
It also
reminded me
of who I used to be…
the singer
Julian.
I know.
I won't leave this place alive.
Don't say that.
Really, I won't.
So…
I want to go out with the choir
and see the world
one last time.
Okay.
The wind of growing up
Gently blows
Carrying the past forward
Evening dew, morning bloom
Lightly kissing the world
Smiling at the past
Long Legs, this one's you.
Your families can get tickets.
Remember to tell them.
Tears fall from the sky
Longing blooms on the ground
People part in a hurry
Who knows when we'll meet again
Did you get your tickets?
Relax. No problem.
Been a while since you kissed me.
HU MEI-HUA
Are you the birth mother
Ms. Li Hui-Zhen?
Is that Yun-Shi?
Yes.
Where is she?
She's in the temporary nursery.
So…
I can't see her?
No.
Ms. Li Hui-Zhen.
Do you agree to place your child,
Li Yun-Shi,
in the care of Ms. Tseng Ya-Han?
Ms. Tseng.
Please.
You must fix Yun-Shi's eye,
okay?
I will.
Ms. Li Hui-Zhen.
Thank you.
If you agree,
you will no longer have custody
of your child.
Legally,
you will no longer be her mother.
Tears fall from the sky
No trouble outside.
I won't go easy on anyone.
Longing blooms on the ground
People part in a hurry
Who knows when we'll meet again
Lovers, don't say goodbye
Get off in order.
No pushing.
Gosh, we're famous.
-Hello, this way.
-Move quickly.
Head inside.
Move.
Everyone, attention.
Heads down, no looking around,
no talking.
Go.
Line up and move forward.
HOPE CONCERT
Hey, look.
Dad.
Our seats.
Over here.
Okay, you sit in first.
Come on. Wait.
You sit here.
Like this.
Talk faster.
Wearing pigtails today.
Can I use the restroom?
-I need to go too.
-Me too.
Okay, hold on.
I'll say this one last time.
If anyone slips up,
no more show.
We move together. Everyone goes at once.
After we return, no more restroom trips.
-Understood?
-Understood.
Line up for the restroom.
Get to the front.
Okay, slowly.
Move to the side.
To the side.
Why are there inmates here?
What are they doing at a concert?
Just keep to the side.
No need to face the wall.
You need to be clear.
It's just a force of habit.
-Reflex.
-Too well-trained.
Faster.
Restroom.
I can't hold it.
Wait a sec.
So in a hurry.
-For Grandma.
-Where's Sister Wang?
Director-General.
Greetings.
-Hello, Director-General.
-Hello, sir.
Welcome, distinguished guests,
to the Hope Charity Concert
hosted by the Star Gen Foundation
and the Agency of Corrections.
I'm sure you're all excited.
Please take your seats promptly.
Thank you for your cooperation.
-All right.
-It's fine.
You look good. You fine.
Nobody move.
Is something wrong?
There's been a theft.
Everyone, on your feet.
Wait, what evidence?
Search.
-Search what?
-Shut up.
Everyone,
you were in the ladies' room.
We have reason to suspect you of theft.
Cooperate with the investigation.
Don't touch them.
-Stop.
-Brother Chung.
What happened?
The women's choir is acting weird.
What's going on?
They said the choir was involved
in the theft.
The show might be canceled.
Chief--
-Where?
-In the restroom.
I'm in charge now.
Everyone out in the hall, line up.
Move.
Go.
-Hands on your head.
-Let's go first.
Hurry up.
Out. Move it.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Not a sound.
A round of applause for
pianist Li Chien-Lun!
Everyone, excuse me.
There's a program change.
We have to
cancel the choir's performance.
But don't worry.
We'll bring on the next act right away.
Please welcome cellist Na Chi.
Enjoy the performance, and
let's give her a warm round of applause.
Excuse me.
Everyone, listen up.
Strip.
Full body search.
No way.
They still have rights.
You found nothing in here.
Human rights? For a bunch of inmates?
Strip, all of you.
Start the search.
Search.
Please cooperate.
Don't touch me. I'll undress myself.
Hurry up.
Search!
Please cooperate.
Search me!
Stand against the wall.
-Don't--
-Why won't you undress?
What?
-Please don't do this.
-Strip.
What are you doing?
-You.
-Why do this?
Why won't you strip?
I didn't steal anything. Why strip?
What?
Everyone, get dressed.
Get dressed.
Let my people go.
Let go.
-You.
-What?
The evidence of theft?
Show me.
So with no evidence,
you dragged them out,
slammed them to the wall
and forced them to strip?
Even if she were your wife,
show some respect.
What is this?
Are cops this sloppy?
Or because they're inmates,
you assume they stole it.
We didn't steal it.
We just went to the restroom.
I trust my people.
Calm down.
We're just following procedure.
-All right.
-Let me tell you.
If any one of them stole,
I'll take full responsibility.
But without sufficient evidence,
this is excessive force.
I'll have your badge taken away.
Excuse me.
We followed the book
during the investigation.
Sir.
We found the ring.
A girl picked it up.
All right, everyone, freeze.
-We're pulling out.
-Wait!
Pulling out?
You think this is a dump?
You think you can just walk away?
It's fine.
Everyone, get ready.
The Director-General is expecting us.
It's over.
Hurry and get ready.
It's fine now.
Applause for cellist Na Chi's
wonderful performance.
Weren't you all excited
about the Sunshine Women's Choir earlier?
Yes.
Here's some good news,
the Sunshine Women's Choir's show
will proceed as planned shortly.
Mom's going on stage.
Ten-minute break.
-So cute.
-Thanks.
You made this and didn't tell us
what it is.
This represents us:
the Sunshine Women's Choir.
-Where does it go?
-On your chest.
Nervous?
Don't be scared.
We're right here.
Just forget it.
Are you ready?
Ready.
You're the best.
Don't worry. You've got this.
Distinguished guests,
thank you for waiting.
Please welcome
the Sunshine Women's Choir
from the Northern Women's Prison
to the stage.
Ten men
Seven are fools, eight are dull,
nine are bad
There's one everyone loves
Sisters, step out
Even if it's sweet talk
Lure him over
Love him well. Don't let him leave again
Then be ready to fall
Falling, falling fast
If love is so great
So great, truly great
Why keep fighting it?
What's the point of struggling?
Am I worse than the rest?
Who's stuck home on weekends?
No one wants to stay home
Watching TV with popcorn
TV and popcorn
I think of the sweet words you said
Was it all a lie
Tears pouring down
Ten men
Seven are fools, eight are dull,
nine are bad
And there's one everyone loves
Sisters, step out.
Even if it's sweet talk
Lure him over
Love him well
Don't let him leave again
Ten men
Seven are fools, eight are dull,
nine are bad
And there's one everyone loves
Sisters, step out
Even if it's sweet talk
Lure him over
Love him well
Don't let him leave
One wrong step for money
I fell into the dark
No excuses, money, food
I risked my life for my kid
Listen to no one
Like I was possessed
Demon-possessed liar
For money, for gain
Fooling myself until I felt nothing
Fuckers like that
Lock 'em up to ward off evil
Gotta change fate
Change, change it up
Quit smoking, gambling
and fix your attitude
Change it all
Stop going mad for money
Now start fresh
Sisters, we fight together
Hold your ground
Don't pretend
No doubt
Listen, don't stray again
Sisters, fight together
Hang in there
Fear nothing, and we've got hope
Demons, get lost
Crazies, get lost
I'll deal with the fuckers
Get lost
MOM, WE'LL BE GOOD AND WAIT FOR YOU.
If there's a faraway place
You are the direction
Too bad regret always lasts
Longer than memories
Longing never ends
But it carries weight
The me that once was yours
I can't forget
Even for a second
I'd trade it for forever
Time will heal our shattered dreams
Goodbyes are too hard
Mend the wounds of parting
May all the heartbreak
Turn us into sunlight
I hear happiness
Happiness singing
Singing of joy and sorrow
All returning to the earth
Like sun and rain, bloom and fade
I've learned to forgive
You left your sweetest dream
Resting in my heart
I hear happiness
Happiness singing
Behind the dark clouds
Ms. Li Hui-Zhen.
Do you agree to place your child,
Li Yun-Shi,
in the care of Ms. Tseng Ya-Han?
Ms. Tseng.
Before the adoption,
may I ask one more favor?
What is it?
Please don't let her know
her mother is a murderer.
Please.
Thank you.
Ms. Li Hui-Zhen.
If you agree,
you will no longer have
custody of your child.
Legally,
you will no longer be her mother.
Do you agree?
I do.
If there's a heaven in this world
You are by my side right now
Never once forgotten
I hear happiness, happiness singing
Singing of joy and sorrow
all returning to the earth
Like sun and rain, bloom and fade
I've learned to forgive
You left your sweetest dream
Resting in my heart
I embrace the past and unhealed wounds
I wipe the tears and promise
not to forget
Love is an eternal light
-Guarding by your side
-By mine
Never once forgotten
I have never
Forgotten.
Sir.
We could…
get in touch with Caring Children's Home,
and bring the girl named Yun-Shi.
The last event was such a success,
so I was thinking,
if we let mother and daughter reunite,
it'll surely draw attention.
Good idea.
Then it's decided.
Yun-Shi.
You were amazing just now.
My name isn't Yun-Shi.
I'm Tseng Zi-Ching.
Right.
Zi-Ching.
What a cute name.
Can I give you a hug?
Mom, is that okay?
Of course.
Just like we practiced before.
Okay.
Auntie, I love you.
I love you too.
Thank you.
This flower pin,
can I give it to her?
As a keepsake of our duet.
Can I?
You can have this.
Do you like it?
This is the only thing I can give you.
I hope you like it.
Thank you.
Thank you for treating her eye.
I promised you.
Zi-Ching, let's go.
Bye-bye.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
Five.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
Five. One.
-Two.
-Three.
Headcount complete.
All right, Workshop Two. Open up.
Move forward.
Sis, what's wrong?
Grandma.
Everybody down. No sudden moves.
8024, what's wrong?
8024.
Workshop Two calling Central.
8024 has fainted. Requesting support.
Grandma, you're awake.
I called your daughter.
She's on her way.
Yu-Wen. A visitor.
Grandma.
I'll go get her.
Wait for me.
Attention, everyone.
Headcount.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
Supervisor.
How's Sis?
Why isn't she back?
Hey.
Why are you packing up?
Don't pack up her things.
Grandma will come back.
-Why pack up?
-Don't.
-She'll be back.
-Don't pack up.
Supervisor.
Don't pack up.
8112.
Sis.
She's not coming back.
8024 wrote this for all of you.
Grandma.
Was Grandma in pain at the end?
Continue.
Was she in a lot of pain?
Grandma.
My dear daughter, Mei-Hua.
I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
I'll get the doctor.
I don't expect you to forgive me.
I only hope
you can be happy.
As a mother,
not giving you the love you deserved
is my life's biggest regret.
For the past 30 years,
I've never stopped
feeling remorse.
Mom.
But I've also never stopped
loving you deeply.
Keep these safe.
Give them only to Grandma, okay?
This necklace.
Grandma passed it to Mom.
If anything happens in the future,
at least this necklace will protect you.
Understand?
Those I once loved
Are you doing well now?
Do you still remember me?
The ones I couldn't let go
Dear sisters,
when you read this letter,
I'll be at life's end.
I thought
the rest of my life
was doomed to be dim.
But because of you,
because of our choir,
My final days were
still filled with happiness.
Till we meet again, take my hand
Sisters, I wasted too much time
living in hate.
And I forgot
I was always surrounded by love.
I want to continue on with you
But time always reaches
The end too soon
Maybe
we may never
undo our mistakes.
But please don't forget
we still have
the ability to love.
Till we meet again
Take my hand
Under a bright sky
It will hold us both
Love is like a gust of wind
Teaching us to let go
We never quite learn to part
But we learned
To let go
The ones we can't bear to lose
Life is far too short.
Cherish every chance to love and be loved.
May you and those you hold dear
find the way
till we meet again.
TO ZI-CHING
Dear Zi-Ching, sorry I can't make
your graduation show.
Happy 18th birthday. My gift to you.
Why a piano?
She doesn't even know I play guitar.
DID YOU SEE THE GIFT?
MM.
I'M SORRY IT TURNED OUT LIKE THIS.
Hot latte.
THANKS MOM
A latte. Okay.
You?
She wants a yogurt.
Yogurt, okay, please wait.
How is it?
Did she read the card?
Ya-Han.
I really don't think you should
lie to her.
Then what can I do?
Tell her the truth.
She'll find out sooner or later.
But I promised Li Hui-Zhen I wouldn't.
Excuse me.
I got it.
How many?
One.
Your mail.
Coming.
For Tseng Ya-Han.
She's not here.
Do you have her seal?
Yun-Shi…
AN ATTACK BREAKS OUT
AT NORTHERN WOMEN'S PRISON
Chief Fang, I'm going to kill you.
Hui-Zhen.
Why is there so much bleeding?
Central, backup.
Chief Fang here.
Send an ambulance to the auditorium.
ASAP.
An attack breaks out
at Northern Women's Prison.
A newly admitted inmate,
during choir tryouts,
attacked prison staff
with a sharp weapon.
The choir leader who stopped the attack
was seriously injured
and taken to the hospital.
Police are investigating the weapon's
-source and the motive behind the attack.
-Are you all having fun?
Yeah.
Next, please welcome
the Dance Club's Super Trio
for a great performance.
Give them a hand.
Let's thank the Super Trio.
Up next
Guitar Club, from Class 3-A,
the pitch-perfect Zi-Ching
who's also my best friend
to perform for you.
Keep that applause coming.
If there's a faraway place
You are the direction
Too bad regret always lasts longer
than memories
Hi, two chicken-leg bentos.
So many toppings.
Thank you.
Hey, you got two mains.
-Trade with me.
-No.
One chicken-leg bento.
Ninety. Grab it yourself.
One grilled-fish bento.
Grilled fish. Okay.
I got it ready for you.
Time will heal what's broken in us
Goodbyes are too hard
This is a card I wrote for Hui-Zhen.
Thanks for your help.
No problem.
No, thank you.
Thanks.
What's this?
Yun-Shi.
Zi-Ching will like it.
Happiness is singing
Singing of joy and sorrow
All returning to the earth
Like sun and rain, bloom and fade
I've learned to forgive
You left your sweetest dream
resting in my heart
I embrace the past and unhealed wounds
ATTACK BREAKS OUT AT NORTHERN WOMEN'S
PRISON, LEAVING ONE DEAD.
Promise not to forget
Love is an eternal light
Guarding by my side
Never once forgotten
Zi-Ching's surgery was a great success.
Congratulations, Ms. Tseng.
Who's hand is this?
I have never
Forgotten
I hear happiness, happiness singing
Let's do our best.
Earn points together.
Get out sooner.
All returning to the earth
Like sun and rain, bloom and fade
I've learned to forgive
You left your sweetest dream
Resting in my heart
I embrace the past and unhealed wounds
I wipe the tears and promise
not to forget
Love is an eternal light
Guarding by my side
Never once forgotten
I have never
Forgotten